{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5ad566ffddddf724f07cf7e1" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5ad47ce2ddddf724f07cf7cf", "ExerciseQuestion" : "ASP.NET webform separates the HTML output from program logic using a feature named as", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ { "Option1" : "Exception", "Option2" : "Code-behind", "Option3" : "Code-front", "Option4" : "None of the above", "Option5" : "Undefined" } ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5aefdfd8d12cbf15f0e33d10" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5aefdb30d12cbf15f0e33d0b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "group", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "precisely and clearly", "Affectionate", "Gently", "Hard working" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Hard working", "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5aefdfd8d12cbf15f0e33d11" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5aefdb30d12cbf15f0e33d0b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "During depolarization, permeability of neuron increases towards", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "group", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "During depolarization, permeability of neuron increases towards", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "N+", "Na+", "Ag+", "Mg++" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Ag+", "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5aefdfd8d12cbf15f0e33d12" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5aefdb30d12cbf15f0e33d0b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Parkinsons disease is of", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "group", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Parkinsons disease is of", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Heart", "Kidneys", "Brain", "Lungs" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Brain", "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5aefdfd8d12cbf15f0e33d13" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5aefdb30d12cbf15f0e33d0b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Genu and splenium are associated with", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "group", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Genu and splenium are associated with", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Medulla oblongata's", "Cerebrum", "Cerebellum", "Vermis" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Cerebrum", "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5aefdfd8d12cbf15f0e33d14" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5aefdb30d12cbf15f0e33d0b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "A mixed cranial nerve is", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "group", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "A mixed cranial nerve is", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Facial", "Abducens", "Anditory", "Oculomotor" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Anditory", "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "true", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Students learn more from a teacher who is", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "admin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b0bca7bdda098241cd1c21c" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5ad47ce2ddddf724f07cf7cf", "ExerciseQuestion" : "The feature in ASP.NET 2.0 that is used to fire a normal postback to a different page in the application is called", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ { "Option1" : "Theme", "Option2" : "Cross Page Posting", "Option3" : "Code-front", "Option4" : "None of the above", "Option5" : "undefined" } ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-04-29T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b27e31d1d7cbd347809f442" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e0e31d7cbd347809f439", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable resource?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "checkBox", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Coal", "Forests", "Water", "Wildlife", "Solar energy", "Biomass energy", "Hydro-power" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Coal", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable.", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b287e173abf0738c47ba006" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e0e31d7cbd347809f439", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Solar energy", "Hydro-power", "Biomass energy", "Geothermal energy" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Biomass energy", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b287ecf3abf0738c47ba00a" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e0e31d7cbd347809f439", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "boolean", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Yes", "No" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Coal", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b287f893abf0738c47ba00b" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e0e31d7cbd347809f439", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "text", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Highly polluting", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy source?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b28813e3abf0738c47ba00f" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e15f1d7cbd347809f43a", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable resource?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "checkBox", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Coal", "Forests", "Water", "Wildlife", "Solar energy", "Biomass energy", "Hydro-power" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Coal", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which of the following is a non-renewable.", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b2881543abf0738c47ba010" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e15f1d7cbd347809f43a", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Solar energy", "Hydro-power", "Biomass energy", "Geothermal energy" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Biomass energy", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b2881603abf0738c47ba011" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e15f1d7cbd347809f43a", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "boolean", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Yes", "No" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Coal", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Identify the non-renewable energy resource from the following?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which among the following is not a renewable source of energy?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b2881703abf0738c47ba012" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b27e15f1d7cbd347809f43a", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "text", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Highly polluting", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy sources", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Which of the following is a disadvantage of most of the renewable energy source?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b28852e3abf0738c47ba01d" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b2883663abf0738c47ba016", "ExerciseQuestion" : "What kind of music do you like more?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "What do you think of Manga?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Electronic music for the win!", "Rock and roll and Guitar is my fave!", "I am eclectic so I don't care any other way!" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "Biomass energy", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "What kind of music do you like more?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "What kind of music do you like more?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b288bb33abf0738c47ba02e" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b288af73abf0738c47ba02d", "ExerciseQuestion" : "How will you use your 2018 tax return?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "How will you use your 2018 tax return?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "I will save it", "I'll spend it on a holiday", "I'll use it to treat myself", "I'll put it toward my mortgage", "I don't know yet" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "How will you use your 2018 tax return?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "How will you use your 2018 tax return?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b288d753abf0738c47ba037" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b288c2a3abf0738c47ba036", "ExerciseQuestion" : "Who do you think is the number one athlete in the region?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "radio", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "Who do you think is the number one athlete in the region?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [ "Emilee Cherry", "Nathan Graves", "Patrick Tiernan", "Mia Stower", "Brodie Croft", "Delissa Kimmence", "Hamish Stewart", "Wylie Buzza", "Steph Hancock" ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "Who do you think is the number one athlete in the region?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "Who do you think is the number one athlete in the region?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35bef13abf075e2860ec5d" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b28869a3abf0738c47ba01f", "ExerciseQuestion" : "The Constituent Assembly was set according to the proposals", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "The Constituent Assembly was set according to the proposals.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "The Constituent Assembly was set according to the proposals", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "The Constituent Assembly was set according to the proposals", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35bff03abf075e2860ec5e" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b35b5153abf075e2860ec47", "ExerciseQuestion" : "What are the tools Techniques used for the Password attack?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "What are the tools Techniques used for the Password attack?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "What are the tools Techniques used for the Password attack?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "What are the tools Techniques used for the Password attack?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35c03b3abf075e2860ec5f" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b35b5813abf075e2860ec49", "ExerciseQuestion" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35c0643abf075e2860ec60" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b35b5b83abf075e2860ec4a", "ExerciseQuestion" : "What are most common tools used to carry as attack Password attacks?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "What are most common tools used to carry as attack Password attacks?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "What are most common tools used to carry as attack Password attacks?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35c0963abf075e2860ec61" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b35b5c33abf075e2860ec4b", "ExerciseQuestion" : "A brief explanation of the criteria that you used to compare the two tools.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "A brief explanation of the criteria that you used to compare the two tools.", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "A brief explanation of the criteria that you used to compare the two tools.", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "What are countermeasures techniques used to counter the attack?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
{ "_id" : { "$oid" : "5b35c1253abf075e2860ec62" }, "Exercise_Id" : "5b35b5cf3abf075e2860ec4c", "ExerciseQuestion" : "How can competitive advantages gained via IS/IT be sustained?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerDisplayType" : "assignment", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerExclusionGroups" : "", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerHints" : "How can competitive advantages gained via IS/IT be sustained?", "ExerciseQuestionAnswerOptions" : [  ], "ExerciseQuestionAnswers" : "", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionCreatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExerciseQuestionDescription" : "How can competitive advantages gained via IS/IT be sustained?", "ExerciseQuestionIsMandatory" : "", "ExerciseQuestionIsProficient" : "", "ExerciseQuestionStatus" : "Active", "ExerciseQuestionSummary" : "How can competitive advantages gained via IS/IT be sustained?", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedBy" : "tcsAdmin001", "ExerciseQuestionUpdatedDate" : { "$date" : "2018-06-15T05:38:59.582+0000" }, "ExQuestion_Id" : null }
